{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_4_4P4A58",
                "player_9_4P4A58",
                "player_5_4P4A58",
                "player_6_4P4A58",
                "player_3_4P4A58",
                "player_12_4P4A58"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                4,
                9,
                5,
                6,
                3,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    732.07,
                    733.227,
                    118.101,
                    0,
                    -53.027438484696546,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    850.614,
                    635.554,
                    118.101,
                    0,
                    6.580123215741594,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    666.793,
                    834.92,
                    118.15,
                    0,
                    -97.64207839018341,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    840.022,
                    837.912,
                    118.101,
                    0,
                    17.736355389595474,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    553.904,
                    575.168,
                    118.15,
                    0,
                    125.52215478992832,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    481.103,
                    597.705,
                    118.15,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            714.446,
            45.066,
            118.15
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1002.7291659663301
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            1206.49,
            329.497,
            118.089,
            0,
            144.3053853968397,
            0
        ],
        [
            714.446,
            45.066,
            118.15,
            0,
            92.35451666461587,
            0
        ],
        [
            227.57,
            901.692,
            118.15,
            0,
            -23.42977792696808,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in floral shirt, the man in blue polo or the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the man in blue polo",
                    "B. the woman in deep V top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the man in blue polo"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in floral shirt, the woman in camo vest or the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in camo vest",
                    "B. the man in grey suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in camo vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the man in blue polo, the woman in floral shirt or the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in floral shirt",
                    "B. the woman in deep V top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in floral shirt"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the man in blue polo, the woman in black vest or the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in black vest",
                    "B. the man in grey suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in black vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in camo vest, the woman in floral shirt or the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in floral shirt",
                    "B. the man in blue polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in floral shirt"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in camo vest, the woman in floral shirt or the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in floral shirt",
                    "B. the woman in deep V top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in floral shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in black vest, the woman in floral shirt or the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the woman in floral shirt",
                    "B. the woman in deep V top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the woman in floral shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the woman in deep V top, the man in grey suit or the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the man in grey suit",
                    "B. the woman in black vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the man in grey suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are positioned close to the ground, either crouching or lying down?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene have a skin tone that is not light?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many female persons are in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a non-standing posture?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men are observed in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a standing position?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the navy blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walk",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. liedown"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the dark V-neck shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. pick_up",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. crouch"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. holding something"
                ],
                "answer": "D. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the front-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. Slightly below and to the front-right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Slightly below and to the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}